What? Hello. It's been a while.
It's been a while.
Good morning, everyone. This is Mukai Mukai.
Today I'm here at the Velma Dome. Today I'm going to be playing the ceremonial pitch for the Lions game, so I thought it would be nice to take some pictures of the practice.
Today I'm going to be playing in the ceremonial pitch for the Lions game, so I thought it would be nice to take some pictures of the practice.
Well then, I'm off to practice now, since I'm allowed to practice now!
Oh, wow!
Wow, I've never been in here before.
Excuse me.
Okay, okay, thank you very much.
Wow.
Lions embroidery.
Wow, it's left-handed.
I want one.
Well, it's far away. First of all, it's far away.
The moment I stood there, I felt like I was suddenly all alone.
I was really anxious about the show.
But when I thought that the audience was cheering me on, I could do my best.
And now that Sunao Tomisato and Kuromi are coming to the show, I really have to work hard.
And my family and friends of my family are coming as well, so I'm going to do my best.
I'm carrying everyone's expectations. I'll do my best.
Have you been practicing? I didn't think I had.
But now that I'm here, I realize that I haven't practiced enough.
But before...
What? Oh!
Good morning!
Nice, huh?
Uh... uh...
You know what I mean?You know what I mean?
Ehhhh! Wait!
Aah! Wait! Aah! Oh, my God!
What? Oh, my...
What? What?
Nice to meet you!
Good luck today!
Thank you very much!
My name is Mukai Tsuruki!
Did you see something? You showed me your number.
That's not me!
No, no, no! That's crazy!
It's not me!
Are you hurt?
If I don't throw strikes today.
I won't be able to come back.
What? Why not?
Please! Throw strikes.
Um, good luck!
Yes, sir! What?
Is it this way?
Then, please!
Can I just throw it the normal way?
Let's do it this way!
Yes!
You're good!
Wow!
Oh!
That's enough!
It's so high!I like it very high!
High!
High?
I see!
Your hands are thicker!
You can do it in no time!
Yeah!
Yes!
That's great!
Sounds great!
Ha-ha-ha.
Really.
Around here, around here.
Yes, sir.
I think he's sitting down.
Do it really high up.
Yes, up there.
Yes!
Right here.
Oh, 〜〜〜〜
Both when I'm not around.
It's hard work.
Well, both of us
A little higher
Yes, sir.
Oh, my God.
That's enough.
That's more than enough.
Here we go.Here we go.
Around here.
Wow! I've got it!
Nice!
Last one.
Right here.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
There are more Lions who are still very good players.
Please support Okada and the others.
Everyone likes him.
You like them all?
No, no, no.
I'll do my best.
I'm rooting for Fukai-san to throw strikes.
I'm counting on you next year.
Yes, I understand.
I entrusted it to you!
Yes, thank you very much.
I'll do my best! Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Are you doing good?
Yes, sir.
Good luck.
Yes, thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
Good luck.
I'm going to pull up to the sleep cheque.
Three, two, one.
Thank you, sir. Good luck.Thank you very much. Good luck.
Yes, thank you very much My favorite player, Okada, gave me a chance to play catch
I didn't think this would happen. I almost cried.
Okada told me to throw strikes for sure.
I'm determined to throw strikes today.
Please do.
You're on the bench.
Is that all right?
Excuse me.
Is this where the players actually are?
Oh, my God.
I was wondering if the players are safe from serious injuries, since they sit here all the time in this heat.
It's hot, but there's a good breeze, so I was a little relieved to find a fan or something.
And if I were a young player who just joined the team, I'd be so nervous that I wouldn't be able to hit the ball if I thought a veteran player was watching me from up here all the time.
I'd be too nervous to bat.
Isn't Mr. Kuriyama sitting over here?
Oh, behind you.
Good morning.
I'm Mukai.
I'm Kuris.
I'll be cheering for you today.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
I had an image of you being over here.
I imagine you've been watching the game from here.
Hello.
It's been a while.
I'm looking forward to working with you today.
I've always dreamed of throwing out a dead ball at a Lions game.My wife told me that it had always been a dream of hers to throw out a dead pitch at a Lions game.
My wife told me.
Yes, sir.
My wife and I have been talking about what we can do.
this...
No? No?
I've collected quite a few things, so please...
Thank you!
Huh? Thank you very much!
This is the director's.
Oh, really! This?
That's the director.
That's great! Thank you!
I'll do my best!
Also, there's Mr. Mocchan.
Mocchan's family is supporting us.
I'm sorry, I only have this one.
I'm sorry, they're all balanced.
I'm sorry, I only have one hand.
Bon appétit! I'm off! I'll take this today.
Thank you for always cheering me on.
Today, I'll be cheering for you even more strongly than usual.
I'm counting on you.
Please do your best today!
Thank you!
Thank you very much! I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
What can I say?
With the help of all of youWith everyone's help.
Absolutely fine.
It's not just my pitching today.
I want the whole game to be great.
I'll definitely win today!
Yeah!It's me. You're going to win?
Yes, I'll be fine!
I'm counting on you.
Yes, please.
Yes, well, pinch me a kambage.
Jankaran!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8
Oh, it's okay, it's safe. Okay, let's go.
Okay, what's that?
I finished my debut with a "ta-da, ta-da, ta-da.
I also used the discus last year.
What?
Oh, that's the wrong one!
Oh! I'm sorry!
Yes, I'm sorry. Thank you!
Yes, sir.
You are now about to
Pang.
BANG.
Boom.
Go ahead.Go ahead.
Applause.
Yes, I'm good.
Slowly, slowly, slowly.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.Next time
Okay, I've changed into my uniform for the show. I'm so nervous I can't talk anymore.
I'm going to throw a good pitch.
You're too nervous.
Okay, I'll stop now.
Again. Again.
Again. Again. Again.
That was perfect.
It's a match.
That's great.
Thank you. I'll try my best.
I'm gonna cry.
I'm gonna cry too.
He's a fan who's been coming to our concerts and handshakes for a long time.
Okada told me to be conscious of going up and up.
So I'm going to be conscious of that.
I'm going to look far away and throw.
Thank you for your hard work.
It looked like garbage and rover.
Good luck.
Yes, I will. I'll do my best.Yes, I will do my best. I will do my best.
Thank you very much.
I'll be back now.
Oh, it wasn't a no-brainer.
I've never thrown a ball like this before.
How do you feel now that you have successfully completed your first Lions remorial pitch?The Lions players said it looked like a no-brainer to me.
So today was a no-brainer.
Well, it was a really great experience for me.
Thank you very much.
Orae Kosora
I just came back from the ceremonial pitch.
As you all know, I think many of you looked like Wamban.
I looked like Wamban, too!
Well, when I stood on the mound, everything was flying out of my head.
It just flew right out of my head.
I couldn't think about anything.
I just threw it.
I didn't think...
I didn't think it would come to this.
But I'm...
I thought the Lions would win because of my failure today.
I think the Lions will win
I think the Lions are going to win.
I think the dance after this
I want to smile and laugh
I want to bring victory to the Lions.I want to deliver a victory to the Lions.
And I am
For next season's fourth grade ceremony
I would like to start practicing again tomorrow!
I'm going to aim for 100 kilometers!
Thanks for watching!
Congratulations on what you just said.
I was a little disappointed.
Was it disappointing?I was so disappointed. I cried a lot.
I thought I was crying.
I cried a lot.
You were so cute.
Thank you very much.
I don't know... Umeda-senpai said she would come,
I worked really hard.
I feel like crying.
I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
I did my best just now.
This was really good.
I'm very happy.
Thank you very much.
Now I'm going to go dance the train dance, and I'm going to wear the same costume as this Blue Legends, and I'm going to dance brilliantly.
Watch me!
We came and danced together before the wedding.
Matching? I'm so happy!
Thank you so much.
I'm sorry.Sorry.
Maille's waiting for you again.
It's so cute.
I'm sick of this.
Is it creepy?
I feel bad.
I'm worried.
Hey, guys.
Good night! Oh, I lost my memory again.
What did I just do?
I don't remember.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun. Thank you so much.
The fans are cheering for you too.
Thank you very much.
It's been a long time ago, but we took a picture together in 2018 or so.
So it's nice to see you.
Let's say, "Pah, pah, pah, pah" here.
I'll be back.
Thank you very much. Promise.
The game is over. It was our second win in a row after yesterday.
At first I was a little down because I didn't do so well on the ceremonial pitch,
The main goal today was not for me to succeed, but for the Lions to win,
I am very happy that the Lions won today.
I was also very happy to see the train dance and the Lucky Seven dance, which were also seen by the fans.
But I definitely want to take revenge again next year for the ceremonial pitch.
I will do my best next time.I will do my best next time.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating.
See you soon.
Please subscribe to our channel.
undefined